That number to me has to be a hundred
trillion in the future. That's how much
that the financial guardrails matter.
And I think Bitcoin, which will stay the
most important of that group, let's
assume it ends up being 33% of
crypto. Well, then you're talking about
33 trillion, a third of it. Let's go
through where it is today at two
trillion-ish. So, you can multiply that
number by whatever you [music] want, 10
to 15, and you can come up with whatever
number you want. It gets you up
somewhere at 600,000 or somewhere
800,000 to
a million.
>> Ladies and gentlemen, my conversation
with Jordi Visser this week is an
important and great one. Jordi talks
about what's going on with Kevin Warsh
at the Fed, why Scott Bessent continues
to try to manipulate the yields down
lower, what's going on with Bitcoin and
its continued rise from the dead, how
you should think about AI, Nvidia
earnings, and many other topics that
transpired over the last seven days.
Jordi's in rare form. He informed me, he
entertained me, and I think he's going
to do the same thing for you. Here's my
latest conversation with Jordi Visser.
All right, Jordi. Bitcoin at 80K, you
got new art, you're back in Brooklyn. I
feel like, you know, all is good in the
world. Uh what are your thoughts about
Bitcoin's historic recovery?
>> Well, let's start with the tape. We had
a uh a huge week, historic week,
multiple standard deviation move as we
talked about last week. And uh we're
consolidating that move. 82,000 is a
natural resistance point. Uh I think
74,000
is the support level that matters the
most when you start getting back towards
the 200-day moving average. And I think
any consolidation here is is good. Um
I think overall, when you when you look
at the tape, uh and I want to make sure
people
kind of take this the the the important
side.
A lot of people reached out to me this
week on
Nvidia.
Marvell reported last night. Nvidia was
up big. Marvell's down.
And they're asking questions like, okay,
um are you adding here? Are you putting
in stuff here? And
I think it's important for people
listening to this to hear my response
because my mindset um
has evolved since June and I've been
more focused on the application side and
the
rise of agent applications and the fact
that I believe the next year is all
about
software that uses agents, applications
and including things like Eli Lilly that
need agents. Everything that's using
agents. Grok Bot is another one of these
uh components. And so I say to people,
if you have a uh
you know, a certain amount of money,
let's assume you have $100 to invest.
I have more money focused on crypto
right now and it's not just Bitcoin.
It's Ethereum. It's Solana. I believe we
are at the agentic application side and
that every year going forward
more and more dollars are going to go
towards the financial guardrails,
towards making sure agents can do
transactions. Uh I think this is where
people's mindset should be. So I view
crypto and Bitcoin and Ethereum and
Solana all having a better opportunity
over the next 12 months
even though I believe that the AI names
that I focus my attention on the
infrastructure side, I still think
they'll outperform the S&P significantly
over the next 12 months. Maybe you get
50% in those crypto names. We did that
in 50 days during the first quarter. So
you have to just realize that right now
momentum is still being unwound. Hedge
funds are still incredibly correlated to
the AI infrastructure trade and we
continue to see deleveraging happening
throughout the hedge fund world because
of the disruption that happened in July.
And so as we talked about a few months
ago, Korea, which was a huge participant
in the crypto market, well, it was much
easier to be involved in the AI market,
and I sent you something this week
highlighting that hey, volumes are
starting to explode in Korea on crypto.
So, I think once we get through a normal
consolidation after a big move higher,
I think you're going to continue to see
this. And I'll just add one more thing
cuz I posted this in X.
Another thing for the tape is now we
have the 200-day moving average pointed
upward in both the Ethereum and Bitcoin.
And if you go back and look at the
times, and I did this, and I posted in
X,
where you stay below
the 200-day moving average for a certain
amount of time, and then you break back
above it, and then it turns up. How does
Bitcoin do from that point moving
forward?
And the numbers speak for themselves. Uh
so, I think we're in the beginning stage
of something that people should be
focused more on a year on, and not just
focused on what's happened over the
course of the last 2 weeks.
>> Now, you mentioned one thing that I I
just want to uh spend a little bit of
time on, which is South Korea. Um there
have been uh some talk of what's going
on in Korea, but I think people don't
quite understand how important that
specific country is to the flows of
Bitcoin and also the AI world. I
remember uh earlier this year I went to
a conference, and there was somebody who
runs a very large company in South
Korea, and he said, you know, all of the
retail investors, they're not talking at
all about Bitcoin or cryptocurrency. And
he was talking about that as like the
industry basically the interest has
died, and all of that capital has
shifted to the AI trade. And they were
going and buying SK and, you know, all
these different things, including 2x
levered, you know, type exposure, etc.
It does seem like it is rotating back,
and maybe even data point that I feel,
but haven't looked at, you know, from
from a quantitative standpoint,
at night, when that uh Korean market
starts to open,
Bitcoin does seem to surge. You know,
even the last couple of days you start
hitting right around the Korean open,
you start seeing Bitcoin, you know, get
a little pop. And so, it are they in
control of the market? Like are is that
the most important country for Bitcoin
right now?
>> No, I I don't think it's the most
important, but I do think it fits in
with something I had talked about uh
at let's say the worst of the bear
market, which was
the first stage of crypto has to be a
combination. It has to be driven by the
energy of retail. And Korea is a big
retail part of the globe. I mean, their
stock market was up significantly and
even with the I mean, the epic fall that
we've seen and all the stories we've
heard about a margin margin accounts
being liquidated and things like that,
I mean, their market is still up more
than almost any other market in the
world. And we're talking 60 plus
percent. So, they matter a lot in terms
of the fact that they definitely have
that energy that you're looking for.
But, retail is the first phase of this.
We also get a lot of short covering. And
you've obviously seen a lot of short
covering in crypto as well.
To sustain a move, Korea itself is not
going to take it higher. What needs to
happen is people from an investment
standpoint need to believe
in the investment side going forward.
And that's why I continue to bring it
back to AI agents. Uh
My video this weekend, I'm I'm in the
final stages of of finishing it up.
But, the YouTube this week
it's the first time that I'm spending
time on Ethereum and Solana. Like, I'm
really focused on the network effects.
I'm focused on tokenization. I think I
mentioned here that I was in the New
York Stock Exchange back in in early
June or late May uh at a tokenization
event. Uh I don't think people fully
grasp what is happening and how
important this is. And it wouldn't
matter that much except for the fact
that the agents are here. So, I want
people to think Korea's just a function
of the same thing happening in the US,
which is retail. The catalyst for this
was definitely Scott Bessent basically
saying we can't handle rates being above
a certain level on the long end And and
doing thing
showing this multiple times over the
course of this month. And so the old
system is showing signs of not being
able to handle rates. At the same time
we have the crypto market going uh-oh,
here we go. There I don't care if it's
printing QE, whatever. This is an
admission that the system is having
problems. At the same time you have the
crypto event at the White House. You
have the Clarity Act that's going on.
All of these things are getting people
to move over, but I would not minimize
the situational awareness month of July,
which took out the momentum kind of
money-making side of retail or the
energy of retail from AI. And I don't
think that AI trade is coming back for
the, you know, the next 3 months.
Meaning I think it's going to be more of
an investor trading market, and I think
the retail community and everyone here
is looking for buy. I do think 82,000
matters a lot. Um I did highlight that,
you know, as of yesterday Solana was up
50% month to date and was the biggest
monthly move since 2024. You're starting
to see
retail it's starting to be more
fundamentally driven and that's what I
care more about is less about Bitcoin,
more about the fundamentally driven side
because that'll bring the traditional
finance investors involved.
>> When we sit down to have these
conversations every week, I always try
to come up with one data point that will
make you smile and be surprised. And I'm
going to use your own framework against
you this week, which is
Dogecoin
is actually up
as of right now 23% over the last month
and Bitcoin is up 22. So basically the
same, but Dogecoin does have a slight
little advantage.
They moved on the same day. I don't know
if anyone was buying Dogecoin because of
Scott Bessent's commentary in the middle
of August.
What is the relationship between
Dogecoin and Bitcoin now?
>> Well, so when I talked about Dogecoin,
what I was really looking for is that it
would break out of a moving average cuz
it sat underneath it. So, it did break
out.
Here's the thing. I think the most
important part of what you're saying for
people to hear,
this move is very fundamentally driven.
I I mean, I've said repeatedly I wanted
to see Ethereum outperform Bitcoin.
Well, we've had a breakout in Ethereum
over Bitcoin at this point. At the same
time, I wanted to see Solana also do
well, and Solana's outperformed Ethereum
recently. This should be fundamentally
driven. This is why I've created an
index with the tokens that are
fundamentally relevant within inside the
space. The meme stuff will be like
GameStop. It'll go through, but it's not
a signal that I care about other than
retail feels like they can be involved
and they can trade this thing from the
long side. What I really want to see is
that it's fundamentally driven. When I
have conversations with people that are
all over the AI infrastructure trade,
when they talk to me about what Nvidia
said, how historic this was, and they
know everything up and down the line,
I always redirect the question, and I'm
I'm telling you they're not there yet.
Okay, you're really smart on this. Where
are you on tokenization, and where are
you on stable coins, where are you on
the payment rails? They're nowhere. The
homework hasn't even been started. This
is why the biggest part of this trade is
from January
until
whatever, August of next year. So, when
I say 1 year that this is going to feel
for me, this is my belief that this will
be like Micron when we were talking
about Micron early last year when it was
60 to 110, and then eventually got up to
1,300. That is the way I feel about
crypto right now is I don't think people
have done the homework yet, the same way
they didn't do the homework on the AI
infrastructure trade, and then you fast
forward a year, now they're all in it,
and they're all frustrated because it's
not going up. To make money in these
types of things where you're looking for
three times, four times, five times, 10
times because of the exponential
innovation,
it has to be on areas that people
haven't done the homework on, and I'm
just telling you for the people I talk
to that manage a lot of money,
they are not focused on crypto and I
think by the end of this year they will
be focused and I believe Solana and
Ethereum, just as a general thing, are
the easiest ones for them to spend time
on because
they're all throughout YouTube, they've
presented at conferences. I'll be
showing videos this weekend that people
should be I think the learning curve is
starting now.
>> It is It is pretty interesting to see
the relationship between these different
different coins. I think you and most
people watching this know that
I'm exclusively focused on Bitcoin, but
I think that the other things have
you know important data that you can you
can glean from.
Kevin Warsh, obviously the new Fed
chairman, he he spoke on Friday morning.
I think that there was some confusion
maybe about his commentary.
On one hand I saw a lot of people being
like oh you know he's leaving room for
there to be rates
rose or risen later this this year and
that's new information.
The other half of people are kind of
like hey this was a pretty boring speech
and there's nothing new here that that
we haven't already heard. What's your
take on his commentary?
He didn't say much that wasn't already
in the
the expectations going forward. I think
what people were looking for is is there
any indication that he's going to raise
rates in September and there was nothing
in there which is not too surprising,
but you're still around 40% chance of a
rate hike in September.
I was looking more to see the movements
and I know people like to look at
equities, but
the best thing to do is the rate the
rates didn't move too much, neither did
the S&P by the time we got on here. But
most importantly the currency stuff was
all within one standard deviation and
the dollar has had a sharp fall. So
dollar yen, which to me is probably the
most interesting because that is the
line in the the line in the sand as the
debate between
whether Besson and Warsh are coordinated
or not.
I think Stanley Druckenmiller,
who Warsh and Besson both
have been involved with, I think he kind
of gave a chance here for Warsh to be
Okay, focus on credibility at the same
time that Besson is trying to clearly
continue the bet that his current boss,
Donald Trump, has, which is we're going
to run it hot and we're going to try to
have the humanoids and the AI agents
create more GDP at a faster pace than
the debt is going to rise. So, I do I do
think Warsh said almost nothing that
matters to me with regards to, unless he
said something where
we're going to drive rates to higher
levels to have inflation come down now
cuz we're not taking any risk. You have
to remember when Jerome Powell was
raising rates, he literally said, I
would not invest in equities. We don't
care about equities. We want them to go
lower because they're a part of the
problem. Financial conditions are as
easy as they've ever been based on where
credit spreads are and where stocks are,
and Kevin Warsh is basically saying, I
want inflation to go back to 2%. Great.
I'm sure if he also said, I want the
deficit and the debt to go back to zero,
that's not happening. So, I think a lot
of this is for showmanship, it's for
credibility at the Fed, but the reality
is I don't think anything is going to
change. We go into September and I want
people to remember this.
Scott Besson intervened in the yen. He's
talked about using the TGA to get rates
down. He's talked about he's talked
about debt buybacks. He talked about
increasing the debt buybacks.
It almost seems like every 3 days he's
jawboning to try and get long-term rates
down, but they're not really moving. So,
if he wants them down,
Kevin Warsh can say whatever he wants,
but I'm going to go with the actions and
the actions are we want rates lower on
the longer end, and I don't think Kevin
Warsh is going to raise rates in
September when Scott Bessent is looking
for the yen to relieve pressure and if
he raises rates in a surprising fashion,
he's kind of offsetting what Bessent is
doing. This speech didn't offset
anything to me.
>> Now, speaking of Scott Bessent,
is this guy like the reincarnation of
Miyamoto Musashi or something where
if you remember there was a photo that
went viral a couple of weeks ago where
he had written like buy $20 billion of
yen or something, right? And somebody
had taken a picture of it and it was it
was the only thing that was written on
the piece of paper.
Very interesting that that was the photo
that was taken and went viral.
Then
we get his commentary of hey, I'm going
to go and I'm going to
double the purchases. I'm going to try
to get the the long-term yields down
etc. And then one of his good friends
happens to write a op-ed that was 100%
written by AI that Druckenmiller
basically comes out and says, no, you
shouldn't do this. The politicians, they
should stop spending money.
Did they coordinate? Like do you think
that there's a high likelihood that
Bessent actually wanted Druck to write
that and critique him in public?
>> I See, I I read it and I think the way
the media has gone with this, I I I
really don't think Stan attacked
Bessent.
I think he attacked Congress. I mean,
how can you blame the person in charge
now when we're at a 6% deficit and $40
trillion of debt? It didn't happen under
his watch and
I think if you sat in a room and having
done that with Stan before and just
having a one-on-one conversation saying,
okay, what would you do right now? Now,
I I honestly don't think and I'll be
covering this this week,
if you ask me because of my belief in
AI,
I honestly would be taking the bet that
is happening within inside the equity
market.
Equities are growing rapidly.
PEs are going down.
That's kind of the thing that's
happening is we're getting into a world
where the stock market is discounting a
very, very different future than we all
realize. It's changing terminal value.
Terminal value is out 3 to 5 years. I
don't think you can look at the debt and
deficit problem the way it is today
and not think that it the next 5 years
are very, very different than just
extrapolating numbers out. We have
exponential innovation happening on one
side. We have profit margins exploding.
We have humanoids on the horizon.
I I know people don't believe this cuz I
can see it after I posted something on
this this week.
If you're doubting the speed of AI, if
you're doubting what AI agents are going
to mean, I I believe there will be
higher corporate taxes in the future
because of humanoids to help pay down
the debt. Whether or not that happens,
that's my belief. I think what Stan was
doing was basically speaking as someone
like Paul Tudor Jones did in the fourth
quarter of last year
that Congress is a disgrace. The
polarizing situation of just spending
money without ever taking any
accountability is getting it in there.
But at the same point,
there isn't much choice. The stock
market is 240% on its way to 300% of
GDP. These companies are making an
enormous amount of money. We have a
distribution of wealth problem in the
country that has people voting
socialist. Like everything is changing
and I don't think having long-term
yields go up to 5 and 1/2% is going to
change that. I think what he said that
was important is it is the one gauge
that theoretically measures the the
fiscal disciplinary side of what's going
on. Rates should absolutely be higher in
a perfect world, but the problem is with
the situation we have. They just can't
let rates going higher. It's opening up
Pandora's Box. So, I don't think he he
attacking Bassin as much as he was
attacking Congress.
>> Yeah, my guess is that's kind of why I
think that maybe Bessant was he approved
of this getting written or maybe
encouraged Trump to to write it, right?
Was this idea of like you're not saying
anything I disagree with. Like you're
actually saying the exact same thing
I've been saying but coming from you
who's not inside the administration,
maybe it'll catch people's attention
more.
>> Yeah, I
See, and I think this is where the
crypto side really merges in. I think
when you go through what Scott Bessant
believes needs to happen. And if there's
one difference between
Stan and Scott. Stan is a hell of a lot
more wealthy than Scott is.
And there is an issue with that because
whenever Scott speaks, he is speaking in
the
the Donald Trump way of the
redistribution of wealth in the country.
And so when you have a very wealthy
person who's made his money in the hedge
fund world and you have someone who's
now a servant of the people, I just
think that there's a different message
that is probably happening for people
here that they should probably read
through. The reason I brought up crypto
into this, I really do believe the
administration and Scott in particular
fully believes in reading his writing,
having, you know, mentioning that he
he's quoting Satoshi. I you have to
really understand that there you don't
have to agree with it, but I happen to
believe it. I happen to believe that
stablecoins are a reflection that they
will almost all be dollar-based. Having
lived in Brazil, having sat in a room
with Michael Milken where he we debated
something and he looked at me and he
changed my view on something for life.
If you open the doors to America for all
eight billion people on the planet,
there will be a line that will be
never-ending. And I've it's true. And
that just means that what forget the
country, forget the president, forget
all this. It's something about America
and the dollar that matters. And so I
believe stablecoins will be dollar based
for the people that are seeing their
currencies, which is the majority of
people on the planet,
be taken by the government. And so if
you believe that's the case, and you
believe that his angle is, "Okay, we got
to keep the basis trade going cuz the
hedge funds got to keep buying
treasuries. We got to let the banks buy
treasuries, so we got to get
deregulation on the banks so they can
buy more treasuries. We've got to do
whatever we can do with the repo market
and everything else to do this. And oh,
by the way, we need stable coins to be
up to $3 trillion so they can buy
treasuries as well." All to let the
humanoids and the speed of AI get us out
of this problem. It doesn't mean it's
going to work, but I do believe that
that's the bet, and I think that's how
crypto is directly connected to
this situation.
>> Today's episode is brought to you by
Arch Public. Arch Public has just
expanded its agentic trading platform
beyond crypto, so pay attention. This is
a big one. Now, they are automating
strategies across stocks, commodities,
and ETFs, and I think that this is going
to be huge. You can now automatically
take profits when one market hits new
all-time highs and rotate that capital
into other markets showing more [music]
opportunity. Whether you're rotating
capital into AI stocks, gold, if you're
investing in the S&P 500, or you're
accumulating Bitcoin, Arch Public brings
real discipline and automation to your
investment strategy. Additionally,
they've launched a powerful new tax loss
harvesting tool. With crypto being so
volatile and its exemption from the wash
sale rule, Arch Public can offset gains
with losses without compromising your
long-term positions. It's exactly what
every serious investor does.
Institutional-grade automation that
works across every major asset class.
There's no more emotional trading, no
more missing tax opportunities, just
smarter, hands-free execution of your
preferred strategies. Go to
archpublic.com
right now. Connect with their team, set
up a time, bring your account in if
you'd like, then you can learn what
automated trading can do for you.
archpublic.com
>> Now, I interviewed one of the
AI safety experts earlier this week, and
and Roman is a professor at
a University of Louisville.
He coined the term AI safety.
He really I think is sought after for
his thoughts on AI and our inability to
control AI etc.
In my research leading up to that
interview I was surprised to find that
he's a very big bitcoiner. And as I
talked with him I think I understood
more as to why he believes Bitcoin and
AI are so related or intertwined. After
you listen to the interview you reached
out to me and said hey we actually have
a lot of overlapping thoughts and you
even used AI to kind of analyze a little
bit in terms of his views and your
views. Talk a little bit as to maybe you
finding a kindred soul like a long lost
brother in in your view of these two
technologies.
>> Um so
one of the funny things about this and I
didn't I didn't give you this backdrop.
My son
who again is is heavily involved in
building AI agents in his internship and
doing all this work. He sent me a an
unsolicited text
uh
about Roman.
I I didn't know who Roman was at that
point. No idea.
And he literally said what do you think
about this? Now I had to ask him exactly
which part he meant because
he's also said that there's a 99.99%
chance that the human race will be
destroyed by AI. So you have to you have
to go through that that was before I
even saw that you interviewed him. My
son had sent me this days before. So
when I saw that you had interviewed him
I went to go watch it and I was
immediately taken aback because aside
from his
in fact I sent you the comparison aside
from his kind of negative end game on
this whole thing that he's got the Elon
Musk where Elon Musk has it as 20% this
guy has it as 99.99
there was so much overlap in our beliefs
but not just our beliefs. I wrote and I
released a substack this week saying the
silent IPO a paper that I wrote last
year on the fact that the distribution
of Bitcoin, this was the normal time
when the technology is not ready yet.
And this gets directly into AI agents.
So,
your interview with him, every step of
the way, what AI agents are going to do,
the disruption to public stocks and
public companies, the inability for
people to compete, the disruption that
will happen, the fact that the financial
guardrails need to be changed, that AI
will destroy all certainty, all trust.
Everything fits into the blockchain and
fits into Bitcoin. And so, when I saw
that,
he's basically talking the same thing.
You have to invest in scarcity at this
point, which I believe in. So, if you
take what he said and you take what I
wrote and you just summarize it into,
let's say, or I I I make it simple in
two levels, he's been an AI safety
expert and renowned, from my little
readings, all the way back to when
machine learning really started to take
off. So, in 2010 to 2013 is when he was
being interviewed on this. He was
interviewed on Diary of a CEO last year,
and that's where I saw it. That one had
like 20 plus million views.
Um, if you take his conversation then
versus one, the one big thing that he's
come to is Bitcoin, meaning this is
something that he absolutely believes
now is a hedge in the same way that I do
against you get AI up to a certain
intelligence, that's what we've been
spending time doing for the last 15
years. So, you have to remember, to get
it to an IQ of 150,
you have to have all of this compute
power, you have to have all of this
training, you have to get it there.
That's where we are. At that level, that
allows AI agents to come, but eventually
you get to recursive self-improvement,
cuz these guys are going so fast and
they're working 24/7 and they're solving
all problems, because they're getting
smarter at the same time that there's
billions of agents, that eventually you
can't humans can't compete with them.
And so a company that is an organization
with lots of people
cannot bolt on AI to survive. So, if
he's right and I'm right
there is at least some probability that
the two of us coming one from a capital
markets perspective, one from an AI
coding perspective, there is no overlap
between our views other than this thing.
I believe
this is where if you say what percent of
money should you hold in crypto or in
Bitcoin
forget a number, think of it as a
probability. What is the probability
that your investments will be disrupted
by AI? If you believe it's 5%, then put
5% in Bitcoin. If you believe it's 50,
then 50. Whatever the number is, it's
your own personal level, but that's the
way I think if you take what he said
what I wrote about this week, not ever
hearing the person. I just thought it
was amazing the connection between the
two things.
>> I am
uh when I looked at the AI comparison of
your thoughts, that was uh my exact
takeaway as well. Is uh two people from
two different worlds coming to a very
similar conclusion. Usually is a pretty
good sign that uh that there's more
investigating to do there.
Um speaking of investigating, the stat
of the week
Nvidia is now doing more than a billion
dollars of revenue per day.
I just want to let say everyone think
about that for a second.
One billion dollars per day in revenue.
I mean, this is insane.
What was your takeaway from their
earnings?
>> I think the biggest takeaway was just
how
far above the street they are for next
year in their own views. And most
companies
that are growing like this, they usually
are somewhat conservative um to leave a
little room for beating the numbers.
I mean, we're
we're talking about 70% rev next year.
Like so when you're doing a billion
dollars a day and then you think the
growth rate is still near 100% near
doubling.
I I I mean it's just an it it's
something that you can't believe but
then when you throw in the fact that off
2027 earnings
with the earnings revisions that
happened in the in the minutes after. I
was looking at it this morning. Uh I
believe now for 2028
they've got uh
$20
for earnings on a $220 stock. So the PEs
going out for a company still growing
their revenues at this pace. I mean this
is the opposite of the dot com bubble
where Cisco was trading at 100 times PE
and Nvidia's called the Cisco of this
time. You still have Michael Burry not
none of the perma bears. Nothing could
happen in the report for them to change
their mind. It's actually hilarious to
go through X and they go searching for
something in there. See circular
finance. I told you.
I I just I don't understand how um
people cannot be just shocked and in awe
of the fact that okay this is what
they're doing. We now have compute
futures are out there. They have all of
the prices of the chips and the compute
going forward further ahead. If everyone
gets the chance uh I don't know if I
mentioned this to you and kind of
sending you what I thought was
interesting from the week from my side.
Uh
the Patel
boys
uh the roommates Dwarkesh and Dylan
phenomenal one hour talk in the the the
the summer doldrums of the last week of
August. Uh amazing conversation and they
just talked about so many things that
are so important on this front. They
didn't mention open source as a threat.
I mean this is two very smart people.
One who interviews the smartest people
in Silicon Valley and has to do his
research and he's renowned for doing
insane research on these things,
understanding it a very high level, but
then also his roommate
who he plays video games with, who's the
number one guy in semiconductors at the
heart of it and data centers. Um to hear
them talk about what's going on and
basically say that we won't have enough
compute ever. And if you guys get a
chance to listen to it, this is also
about OpenAI and Anthropic and the fact
that
there's a really interesting point that
they have such high margins that they
have the ability of paying for all of
the compute that comes online
because they have orders coming in for
their intelligence, which is far better.
So this is a very, very unique situation
that could end up with a monopoly to
some degree on compute with OpenAI and
Anthropic. So if you're looking for a
reason why Anthropic is going public,
why OpenAI is going public, these guys
alone are going to be the ones that need
all of the compute. And so all of that
lines up with there's just we're we're
still in this thing where there's
insatiable demand for compute and most
people are scared of this and worried
about it.
>> You know, what's interesting to me about
um
these conversations is um
it's not just what I'll call market
commentators, researchers, podcasters
talking about what's going on,
but you also see the people who are
driving the industry sharing clips and
podcast episodes of those people. So
it's almost like there is as much uh
learning from the commentary group from
the leaders of the industry as there is
the industry leaders learning from the
commentators.
And I I think back to
I don't know, 15 years ago,
there was not this much like
open-sourcing of knowledge and
information. And so people talk about,
you know, uh the technology innovation,
the talent, the, you know, uh obviously
the abundance of intelligence coming
from AI. I actually think the amount of
content on the internet is accelerating
everyone's lessons learned.
And it is a huge driving factor of why,
to your point, there's almost like this
machine time now.
Right? Is you basically have Elon Musk
going on a podcast or Jensen going on a
podcast, and they explain in great
detail. And that gives an idea to five
entrepreneurs who then figure out, "Hey,
I can go take, you know, this and do
this." And next thing you know, they
push the pace of innovation. But then
they go on a podcast, and then Jensen
sees a clip online, and then he's like,
"Hey, well, based on that, we should be
doing this."
And so it does feel like, um, there's
this hive mind online that is all
working on a group project. And the
group project is like, how do we build,
you know, uh, ASI or AGI? And then how
do we also build all the infrastructure
necessary to run this?
And it's pretty cool, frankly, just to
watch this all play out, because you
would never have access to these people,
you know, without the last 15 years of
like the digital content world, uh,
getting to the point that it is.
>> So, this is an important point, um, that
you're making. And while you were saying
it, um,
the way my brain works is I start
thinking about a lot of things that are
connecting dots for me. So, I want to go
back to something I've said a lot and
take it into why I'm doing what I do.
Um, cuz people have watched this now.
We've had We We have consistent numbers
of viewers. So, they they know us. They
know you, for sure. They've gotten to
know me. And I've said that I hated
school growing up. And the reason I
hated school,
I definitely have, um, the ability to
process an enormous amount of
information in a short amount of time.
Which means the downside is I get very
bored in static environments where it's
taking too long. Um, so if you think
about what's happening in the world
right now like
a sporting event.
And you watch a football game,
and then Goldman Sachs and Morgan
Stanley, all they do is tell you the
score of the game at the end. Nvidia
beat earnings by this, these are the
highlights.
But if you watch the game,
maybe the Giants won the game by 20
points, but you know they lost the
yardage game. Uh they they lost the uh
the turnover battle. They were lucky to
win because there were three bad
mistakes on the other side. So you've
watched the nuance of the game. What
podcast X and all of this real-time
information is is like watching a game
and getting all of the nuances within
it. And all you're getting from the
banks,
someplace I work, by the time it goes
through the legal scrumming, the
bureaucracy of the place, the amount of
phone calls, there's no way you're
getting real-time information. You're
getting some kind of a BS summary. So
the reason I decided not to work in the
hedge fund world anymore,
my choice. People call still now because
I built the business and like, "Why
don't you come here? You can help us.
We'll pay you money and do this." I
don't want to work for anyone. I don't
want to manage anyone, but part of the
reason is because I'm learning so much
by using Grok Bot all day, by using each
of the AIs. Doing the videos I do each
week forces me to do the homework on
everything that's going on. That's why I
said right now most of my time is
shifting towards Solana and Ethereum. I
already know why Bitcoin will be
something. I've already proven to myself
that Bitcoin is just the S&P 500 of the
future. It's the purest AI trade. It
represents the ecosystem of crypto, but
in the purest sense, the ecosystem
should not be forming when we start
transitioning to where the crypto
guardrails are actually being used and
deployed. And the only way they can be
used properly is by AI agents. For those
of you haven't seen this week, Elon
Musk, when someone asked, "Hey, I want
to use Grok Bot for bank account." He
said, "Oh, okay, yeah. Here's what we'll
do. If you guys are worried that your
money's going to be stolen by your AI
agent, xAI will guarantee you your
money. Just go use it." He's trying to
get entrepreneurs to use this stuff. The
banks aren't able to do this. They're
not able to be on top of this. So, I
just think when you're thinking about
the world and particularly with your
children, if you have someone that seems
a little bit ADHD, they're able to
consume a lot of information. If they go
to school, they're trying to get their
brains to stay within side a vertical
and actually get a major and do this.
Part of what's going on is you can learn
multiple things very quickly, connect
dots, and that's why I always say, if
you want to have an AI mindset, you have
to think like a Quantico grad, not like
a Harvard grad. You have to be able to
think about things that are outside the
box that maybe you're not thinking, that
are all thinking in bets. It's why I
recommend you getting Annie Duke's bet
book. You have to really be Bayesian in
the approach you have. New information's
going to come in all the time, and you
have to be willing to say, "You know
what? I'm worried about open-source. You
know what? These numbers on Why would we
care if Anthropic's numbers are 67 or
72? What does that actually mean at the
end?" You guys are trying to take
exponential growth and convert it into
some linear thing where historically
it's meant like to be able to do that, I
think you have to be doing what you're
saying, which is stay on top of the
podcast, see everything that's
happening, because what happens in a
week is what used to happen in a
quarter, and that just means the game is
moving so fast that you can't get just
the final score and actually know what's
happening.
>> Do you worry on the Nvidia side,
um
it's only up 25% over the last year?
You know, one one year, 25% given the
growth rate, given, you know, all the
stuff that they were talking about, how
exciting it is,
I think a lot of people would think that
it should be up more.
Is that a bullish sign? Hey, it should
be up more, it's not, and there's more
for this to run? How [clears throat] do
you look at, you know, 25% obviously is
a big number given how big the company
is, but but still it's not like it's up
50, 60, 70% like their growth rate is.
>> So, two two things just regarding um the
investing side that fit in with the
first conversation we had uh about
crypto and Bitcoin.
Pa- part of what drives a um a stock is
how many people already know the
situation and how many people are
already involved. The second thing is
opportunity cost.
Right now, there's a lot of stocks going
up a lot. And they're attracting a lot
of dollars. To move Nvidia right now,
it's
I mean, $5 trillion is not an easy thing
to move around. Like it's it it takes a
lot of dollars, marginal dollars, to get
that thing to move. This is why I always
say, Nvidia is what? Almost two times
the size of the crypto market cap.
Like it's much easier to go buy crypto
and say, "Hey, I think it's going to
go." So, opportunity cost number two.
Number three, and probably most
importantly,
do I think that Nvidia 5 years from now
that their business will be able to grow
at this pace? Absolutely not. Um do I
think right now we're in the sweet spot
of the infrastructure buildout? Yes. We
are absolutely in this.
Do I think that there will be
competition? Jalapeno was released or is
being used by Open AI.
It's not going to disrupt their numbers
this year. It's not going to disrupt
them next year. But when you go through
what happened, for those who don't know,
this is a chip designed by Open AI by
AI.
At some point, the design starts
happening. And then when humanoids start
going on, the question is,
will the advantage that Nvidia has had,
the moat that they've had with CUDA and
with the designs and how quickly they've
brought them out? Will this get to a
point where number one, this all
changes? The second thing is, will we
get algorithmic efficiencies to where we
don't need as much Of course we will. Um
it's a very inefficient system. The
human brain does far more calculations
than this can. We need more power to do
that. So, when you listen to Gavin
Baker, when we actually go on the edge
and we're able to do
the kinds of work we need, and people
don't actually need that much. We're not
there yet. We still have another three
to five years of needing a lot. So, the
fact that it's this cheap to me means,
"Hey,
30% a year is a good return." So, when
you say it's up this much, I I bet by
the end of the year, we will have
outperformed the S&P. And again, Nvidia
has outperformed even though it's been
stuck in the mud over the course of the
last two years, I think the AI
infrastructure names are going to go
through the same thing. You have to
think hard about this terminal value
thing. Go read the paper I wrote on the
Xilinx IPO. If you don't truly have
scarcity, which Nvidia right now has
scarcity, but at some point, five years
from now, six years from now, it won't
have scarcity, the value of Nvidia is
the total sum of the future discounted
cash flows. If all of the sudden, that
PV starts to change cuz you're like,
"You know what? We won't need any GPUs
in 10 years."
Well, then Nvidia is not going to be
worth as much as it is. So, I just think
that's what's going on with Nvidia, and
I think people should pay attention more
and more to this concept of what's true
scarcity in a world of AI.
>> Now, this idea of scarcity, I think has
become um obviously a debasement trade.
If I look I was just looking at the
Google trend data, and you look at uh
interestingly, the phrase money printer
has pretty much become a meme and is
fairly consistent in the uh search
trends since 2021, you know, give or
take.
Debasement looks like it exploded in
popularity, it fell, and now it's coming
back. So, the idea of debasement to me
is more of a index on the investment
theme, whereas money printer is like a
social construct. It's It's like a meme,
right?
I am surprised
as to how much the debasement trade idea
had kind of dissipated now looking back.
But, it feels like it is rapidly showing
up and people saying, "Hey, oh my god, I
forgot about this almost. Like I need to
go buy this." Bitcoin and gold
correlation is the highest it's ever
been.
Do these two assets just become
you know, almost proxies for each other
at some point? Or do you see investors
putting money in their portfolio into
Bitcoin or gold for different reasons?
Like is there Or are they just married
together in in that correlation we
should expect to stay as high or higher
going forward? And it's just like the
debasement trade is one big trade? Or do
you see some sort of difference between
maybe Bitcoin and gold?
>> Uh so, the debasement trade is the
narrative. I believe this is about
scarcity. So, um those are the two If
you had to pick which two assets are the
definitions of of scarcity,
those are the two that have been
chosen. I mean, there's no other way
around it. Bitcoin has been chosen as
the digital store of value, and gold has
been chosen as the store of value. So,
if you believe that there's going to be
abundance, and every day that we get
closer to AI agents, that we get through
all this stuff, you can disagree with
the end result of the way Elon Musk
describes abundance,
but there's no way to say it's not
closer to occurring. There's just no way
to say that. Anyone who's used AI,
and who's managed people before, I can
run a business where I can do a lot of
things without needing a person, and I
used to need people for almost
everything that I did. What you
described at the beginning in terms of
Grokbot, and being able to have now
specialists, when I want to set up a
task to do, I just tell my chief of
staff, "Go put this together." It
doesn't matter what it is. That's why
this weekend, uh one of the things I'm
doing for the subscribers is I literally
built a prompt for Grokbot, and you're
going to be able to do a free trial. I I
I don't know when they started it or if
they've started it yet, but even if you
get rid of your other LLMs for a month,
or don't go out to you know, dinner or a
game or whatever, a movie, whatever you
spend money on. The $200 for Grok Bot
for a month to just be able to take the
prompt that I gave you and see what it
can already do that you can have
specialists that are tax people, that
are whatever you want. And these little
cool little agents sitting there. The
problem I think people have is, well,
how do I do that? And I'm giving them
the thing of all you have to do is put
this in, it will do it for you. That's
the whole beauty of it. So, I I I don't
believe in the debasement side. I just
think it's a narrative to give people
happiness on this.
I believe the old system and the new
system are merging. One system is based
on a cost structure that is zero, the
other one is based on friction and
humans. And to get those two to merge,
there needs to be a narrative and the US
dollar or as Druck said,
if you're going to manipulate long-term
yields or attempt to,
that has huge implications for the
entire world. You're keeping monetary
policy too easy at a time where the
normal rate should be,
let's say above nominal GDP. Nominal GDP
right now is 6% and I think it's
understated. So, at 6%, we theoretically
should have 10-year yields, let's say at
least at 6%.
We don't have them anywhere there. We're
focused on like where are yields
relative to inflation. There was a long
time ago in the '90s where you go back
and look where rates were
a heck of a lot higher than they are now
when nominal GDP was the same level. So,
I just think this debasement thing is a
narrative for it. I believe this is
about the world's merging and about
scarcity becoming something that people
want to invest in and abundance is
coming to destroy other things.
>> Today's episode is brought to you by
Simple Money. Bitcoin mining has a
reputation for being complicated, risky,
and hard to evaluate as a real
investment. If you're considering mining
in 2026, what actually matters isn't
headline profitability, it's uptime,
repairs, and whether the operation is
run like a real business. That's why
I've been using Simple Mining. They're
based in Cedar Falls, Iowa, and they run
a white glove hosting operation where
you own your miners. You choose your own
pool, and you have Bitcoin sent directly
to your wallet. They were featured on
the Inc. 5000 list as the fastest
growing company in Iowa with over 40,000
machines under management. What stands
out [music] to me is execution. They
have the number one rated ASIC repair
center, and for the first 12 months,
repairs are included. If mining margins
get tight, you can pause with no
penalties. And if you want to resize or
upgrade your fleet, there's a
marketplace to resell [music] equipment
instead of being stuck. To help people
think it through whether mining actually
makes sense right now, they put [music]
together a short resource called the
2026 Bitcoin Mining Blueprint. It walks
through the five mistakes [music]
investors make when allocating to
mining, and they also explain how to
avoid them before deploying capital. If
it sounds interesting to you, you can
get it for free at simplemining.io/pomp.
That's simplemining.io/pomp.
Go check it out today and see if you
should get into the mining game.
>> Now, one aspect that I see people
talking about online is this idea of AI
agents using crypto. Um, I do think that
we have talked in the past about this,
and one aspect that I keep coming back
to is Bitcoin is actually not that great
for payments. Maybe for really large
payments uh it could be uh valuable.
Obviously, we now see um stablecoins
becoming much more popular, and I think
that both traditional finance and agents
you know potentially could use that.
But, I see a whole slew of new companies
and new projects trying to figure out
like what is going to be the money for
the agents.
Do you have opinions, or have you spent
time there? And less on like the
framework of agents need, you know,
money, and more so on like is it
something that already exists in the
world, or is it something that is net
new that's kind of custom built for the
agents?
>> Well, at this point my mindset is very
simple. Stablecoins are
the transaction side. Um Bitcoin is
absolutely collateral. It is a store of
value. It is something that as the
lending markets grow, as we talk about
Coinbase this week, mortgages, like
posting Bitcoin for mortgages.
Again, if you have and you think about
what goes into a mortgage, what do they
do to determine whether you're a good
credit risk?
They assume the job you have today is
the job you'll have tomorrow. They
assume the income you have today is the
income you'll have tomorrow. They assume
the assets you own will be the assets
you have tomorrow. And a lot of those
assets and those jobs are illiquid. You
couldn't get out of them if you wanted
to. So, what is Bitcoin? Well, Bitcoin
tells if it's posted and it's
collateral, well, you know where you
stand real time. There's liquidity. You
can get in it. You can get out of it.
And this is why I think you have to
separate what's going to happen from
transactions,
tokenization will allow everything to go
on chain and have value and be able to
move at speeds that allow it again
to immediately get net worth.
And it's not, you know, I've been doing
a lot more listening and I do recommend
I don't I Have you had Tom Lee on?
I'm sure you have.
>> of times, yeah, yeah.
>> I I think Tom because
he worked in traditional finance and has
for a long time and thinks that way,
uh and he was at Kidder Peabody, which I
have a lot of respect for people I've
worked in over the years that started at
Kidder Peabody. Um I I just think when
you listen to his thought process on
Ethereum and tokenization, when you
listen to Vlad at Robinhood, and you
really start to spend time on how they
envision this happening with
tokenization,
there's a lot of assets which have no
value that are worth money. IP is worth
money, but there's no way to transact in
it. How do you If you have IP and you
want to offer it to someone to buy, how
do you do that? That was my original
attraction to understanding the value of
tokenization, of crypto, of getting rid
of the middleman and making sure that if
Justin Bieber didn't want to give his
money to Scooter Braun by signing a
contract with him and giving up 90% of
what he would had already created, but
being able to keep 80% letting the
community have 10 and having it
programmable, all of a sudden everything
changes. So, I think the answer to your
question is I wouldn't overthink this
too much. Um stablecoins have already
been chosen as of now as the transaction
side, which Bitcoin couldn't do. So,
they've replaced what Marc Andreessen
wrote in Why Bitcoin Matters.
Where Bitcoin fits in is it is a chosen
store of value. It is the chosen asset
that people migrate to when they're
worried about disruption from innovation
from other things. So, if you don't
believe in Ethereum and you believe
there'll be a better one in the future,
well,
I think that's a higher risk than the
belief of Bitcoin leaving. Bitcoin has
been chosen just like gold was chosen.
We saw we've seen how long gold has
lasted as the chosen store of value.
That's why I kind of break these things
down for people to think about them
differently.
>> Now, we have a lot of people who watch
this who they like Bitcoin.
Um they hold a lot of Bitcoin. They've
held Bitcoin through the euphorias of
the highs and the doldrums of the lows.
They have been through the roller
coaster.
They are hardcore believers. You can't
shake them from holding Bitcoin.
But it does not stop them from
pontificating on the single most
important
question in all of Bitcoin.
How high is it going to go, Jordy? How
high can it go?
>> I
So, I'm I'm I I've I've learned my
lesson after um last year believing we'd
already be at 250,000 and we're not even
close to that. Not to get into direct
numbers, but here's what I'll say about
uh Bitcoin in a in a in a in a
back-ended way.
Um I do believe the transfer of assets
from the traditional fiat system with
terminal value now being disrupted by
agents. That more and more people are
going to increase their holdings in
Bitcoin.
And right now, that is the only place
that I believe that you're going to see
massive retail, wealth management,
pension funds, sovereign wealth funds
again. They will be moving money into
Bitcoin as a hedge against the other
side of the equation, which is let's
just say 700 trillion assets first 3
trillion market caper.
Let's say four. Let's assume we'll be at
four by the time this airs.
Uh so at 4 trillion, that number to me
has to be 100 trillion in the future.
That's how much that the financial
guardrails matter, and I think Bitcoin,
which
will stay the most important of that
group, let's assume it ends up being 33%
of
crypto, well then you're talking about
33 trillion, a third of it.
Let's go through where it is today at 2
trillionish. So, you can multiply that
number by whatever you want, 10 to 15,
and you can come up with whatever number
you want. It gets you up somewhere at
600,000 or somewhere at 800,000 to
a million. So.
>> So, I am uh that's a big number, and I
think people will be excited to hear you
even talk about that number.
Uh I'm looking right now for what the
Bitcoin percentage of
um
What is the Bitcoin percentage of the
total market? And if I just do some
rough math real quick,
um
it looks like Bitcoin
is
somewhere in the ballpark of about 50%.
I'm looking there's different numbers
different places, but um
it's over 50% actually. All right, total
market cap I'm seeing right now is 2.7
uh trillion, Bitcoin's 1.6.
>> Mhm.
>> I don't know if Bitcoin goes below 50%.
And
part of this is like
if you actually take out
all the things that have no value
meaning that, you know, it's like if
somebody created some scam coin that
has, you know, $50 million market cap
but like everyone is convinced it's
actually a zero and it's just like bag
holders and there's no liquidity. You
take all that stuff out
Bitcoin may be closer to like 75 80% of
the market.
Right?
To have held that big of a percentage of
the market for, you know, I don't know,
17 18 years now.
I almost go to like the Lindy of like
what what would change that all of a
sudden Bitcoin be less than 50% of the
market? Right? So again, like whether
it's 33 or 50 or 70, it almost doesn't
matter. It's a It's a big percentage,
but I do think that if you're correct
and the entire crypto market goes to a
hundred trillion
Bitcoin may be a bigger percentage of
that and would be, you know, obviously a
bigger number. So if we use your
numbers, that's exciting.
If it happens to be bigger then it's
just like icing on the cake.
>> So let me give you my thought on this
because um
So when I gave you the $700 trillion
dollars
if you go through the breakdown of them
stocks is maybe 150 trillion.
Okay.
So gold is very small.
Okay?
I believe that Bitcoin should be
equatable to kind of the gold plus stock
side to some degree. Now, I believe
stocks are more representative of
innovation, which means that's more in
the Ethereums, the Solanas, and the
parts that are generating cash flows,
generating excitement that people kind
of are gambling on, they're betting on,
they're going through. Well, store of
value is I want to make sure at the end
of the day that my house is stable, this
is stable. This is where I put my money
and that's where the safe investment
goes. So
I can live with you thinking it'll be
above 50. I think for certain the next
stage
you should see a rapid rise in Ethereum,
Solana, and all of the parts that are
for the AI agent side. So, I do believe
in the end that might be the case.
But, I'm going to guess
if we get to 100 trillion over the next
decade and Bitcoin gets to a million
over the next decade, okay?
Um I think that'd be fun.
>> Yeah, and I but I think I do think the
innovation side would have to be driving
a lot of the traditional finance and the
people that control most of the money.
If it were younger people and I asked
you the question saying, "My son
believes Bitcoin back in 2020 was too
boring."
Um so, people are in prediction markets.
Like, I think you're underestimating how
much people like to gamble on things and
how Bitcoin becomes a store of value and
a safety thing. So, for those and again,
I've never sold any Bitcoin. So, I'm
sitting in
you know,
it's not my all Well, actually, it might
be because I've been buying more. So, I
don't really pay attention to how much
it it is of this. I know this,
I have more Ethereum than I've ever had.
Um and that's because of my belief that
I think tokenization and the stablecoin
rails, what Stripe is doing, that the
agents will bring the hedge fund world
in and the hedge fund world needs a
narrative and it's very hard the Bitcoin
narrative is very hard one to
understand. It's much easier for people
to understand value accrual, cash flows,
things like that, and that's where I
think for at least the next three to
five years, I just think the ecosystem
side is going to is going to benefit
more than Bitcoin. That's why I I think
the val- the percentage will go down.
That's my view.
>> I'll leave you with this, which is
there's a belief in the Bitcoin
community that all the speculators, the
gamblers, the shitcoiners could all just
future Bitcoiners. They don't realize it
yet.
>> [laughter]
>> We'll leave it at that, but uh I I
To be clear, I actually think and and
I've been saying for a while that most
of the crypto industry is dead, but I
think that Bitcoin, stablecoins,
tokenization, and like equity
infrastructure is very much real and and
going to continue to accrue value. What
I recently was on somebody's podcast and
they asked me, "Well, what about
Hypoliquid?"
And I said to him, "Look, it's not
equity, but I look at it as
infrastructure." And so, I think there
are some of these like, you know, kind
of tokenization, decentralized,
token-based things that don't fit
perfectly in a bucket, but just like in
the traditional world, there's kind of
very clear
areas where value accrues, there's going
to be the same thing in crypto. And so,
although people may not
be used to me thinking about something
like Ethereum, you know, I started out
mining Ethereum. I understand, you know,
what that value proposition looks like.
It It is a different thing today, right?
It's not GPU-based, it's more
proof-of-stake, all that, but
I don't know. The market has not put it
to zero, and then I think there's data
in that. And so, the people who are like
everything else is going to zero,
you know, doesn't mean that you should
change your theory on Bitcoin or or your
conviction on Bitcoin, but I do think
that when I go talk to all the
institutions, they talk about Bitcoin,
but they talk about Ethereum and Solana
and you know, Hypoliquid and and these
other things as well. And so,
maybe the world's not as black and white
as as the hardcore Bitcoiners want it to
be.
>> Yeah, just always remember one thing,
and I I've I've heard Tom Lee say this a
few times over the course of last 6
months, and I I happen to agree with it,
and it's because we both have worked in
Wall Street in banks.
Uh
there's a value in trust that comes even
if the technology's not the best. Uh and
that is one of the important points when
you're thinking about the guardrails and
the transition we're making. Every
single bank is talking about
tokenization, Every exchange, every
place around the world. Japan just said
they want to be completely on chain by I
think 2030.
These are massive things that are super
important. And when you're dealing with
money and you're dealing with um
people's savings and you're dealing with
assets, they care about speed, but what
they care more about speed is is trust.
This is the reason why we don't have
full self-driving and while by now
everyone must realize that a full
self-driving car
is never drunk. A full self-driving car
might make mistakes, but human beings
makes mistakes every day. But because
the government friction will always be
there until there's no more governments,
the safest thing is to think about the
places not that are the best innovation,
not that makes the most sense. And
that's why I keep migrating back towards
the Ethereum Solana thing because right
now when I talk to people that I respect
in the world that have been business
leaders, CEOs of other companies that
have moved into crypto, when they talk
to me they're mainly talking about
what's happening and the things that
keep being brought up are Ethereum and
Solana no matter where it is. So if I
started hearing something else, I'm in
there. And I get that people are going
to have faster innovations and those
will fit a niche and they will go up in
value as well. I just think when you're
thinking about the framework, you have
to think about what the mag seven has
done. There's not just seven companies
in the S&P 500. There's 493 other ones
that are not as successful as those
seven.
I think you got to start thinking of
concentration within side the crypto
world for everyone there. The whole
ecosystem will go up, but I do think
this is going to be the same situation
where the trust for merging is going to
be very important to the final decision,
not the best innovation.
>> Makes uh makes sense to me. All right,
what uh what are you going to cover in
your video this week? Anyone who is
watching this right now, I never say
pause, but you should pause this. You
should go to Jordi Visser on YouTube,
hit the subscribe button. Help help our
guy out here. He works hard for you, you
know. It's like a nice thing you could
do for him, maybe for his birthday.
>> Uh first of all, um the company that
I've used in my videos for a while, um,
is going to be shutting down OpenBB. And
so, I've had to make a quick pivot uh,
to Google Slides. So, there's going to
be a different, um, uh, presentation,
but I a lot of the stuff we've talked
about, I'm going to go more details. I
am, like I said, Rockbot and Solana and
Ethereum, but also, uh, in terms of the
Bitcoin move, the Druckenmiller thing,
the Nvidia earnings, all of that stuff.
But, the main thing I want to just make
sure people realize,
if you listen to this,
what I do on the weekend, and before
Anthony and I agreed to do this, one of
the things he asked, are are we going to
can we do this on a Saturday and then
release you on a Sunday, or is there
going to be too much overlap? The way,
and I think we've we've learned this,
the way that I approach things is very
different. I I try to tell a story with
data-driven stuff, so you guys can go do
your own research. It's supposed to be
educational, less conversational. Here,
we're just speaking our minds. I don't
have a script, I don't have anything.
The only thing we do is say, "These four
topics seem interesting to me. Bring
whatever else you want to bring." And we
go whatever direction. I have it a
little bit more organized for myself to
be able to give you guys a story that
connects all of these pieces together in
one, almost like a mini book. So, if you
haven't seen it, go see it, but I'll be
covering all of those things. I think
it's the most important time for
understanding. Number one,
the AI trade has reached a different
level where people are crowded into it.
Number two, everyone's looking for what
the next three and five bagger can be,
and they're running out of places to go
find it. And so, what you're left with
at this point, in my opinion, is if AI
agents are the major theme, which
they've been all year, but now the
infrastructure side has been overbuilt,
and everyone knows it. I fully believe a
year from now people will look back and
wish they had paid attention to crypto
at this stage. So, I do think it's going
to hold lows. I think it's continuing to
build a bottom here.
Uh, I think if it does go, it's going to
go fast, and I'm going to cover it.
>> I love it. I love it. I think you're
doing a great job. But you may not be
scripted. Obviously, I'm scripted. Uh
>> That's nice.
>> As uh uh people in the comments they
were like, "Oh, you know, he's a fan. He
he's scripted." Um
All right. We'll talk again next week.
Next week in person. Let's go.
>> In person.